<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christine and Jimmy Take On The World</title>
    <description>Long Form Jekyll theme built with SASS / COMPASS / SUSY</description>
    <link>http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2016 23:57:40 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2016 23:57:40 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.1</generator>
    
      
      <item>
        <title>California NP</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My wall has a new addition, a map of U.S. National Parks. Using tacks, Christine and I have turned the map into a playful game. My color is red, Christine’s is yellow. Green is for parks that we both have visited. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We recently camped at Death Valley and Joshua Tree National Parks, adding two green tacks to my wall. Due to her insistence on counting two parks that she visited when she was young and forgetful, the tally stands at 12-10, Christine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Death Valley&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Numbers can describe some aspects of Death Valley, a desolate landscape that overwhelms you with its size and stark beauty. Spanning more than 3 million acres, it’s the largest park in the lower 48. It&amp;#39;s home to the lowest point in North America, perched 282 feet below sea level. It once scorched 134 degrees - the highest recorded temperature in history. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Death Valley is so vast that landmarks are often 30 minute drives apart - after a 9 hour drive, these minutes were taxing. But along the way, we passed sand dunes and a unique desert palette, looked for the moon behind the mountains and scanned for coyotes before our headlights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/death_valley/palette.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; height=&quot;340px&quot; width=&quot;520px&quot;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;Artists Palette along Artists Drive&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our first stop was a short hike that knifes through Golden Canyon. The canyon walls along the trail are jagged and colorful, decorated by layered patterns. Rivets hint at phantom streams of flowing water. More than anything, the walls are immense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/death_valley/golden_canyon.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; height=&quot;340px&quot; width=&quot;520px&quot;&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Golden Canyon was our first sense of scale: trapped within its barren hold, it&amp;#39;s easy to forget that the canyon is but a tiny fraction of the park&amp;#39;s wonders - a small branch on a Giant Sequoia. Back at the trailhead, the valley expanded again for miles left and right, and the mountains loomed steady ahead. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the sun setting, we hurried to Badwater Basin, famous for  its geography and its salt. The lowest point in North America, the basin is the final resting point for flash floods. The rainwater evaporates, leaving behind salt that accumulates into a wide field of white. Exploring until the sunset leaked through a distant valley, we walked back with a lingering taste of salt in our mouths. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/death_valley/badwater_basin.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; height=&quot;350px&quot; width=&quot;600px&quot;&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Death Valley transforms at night. The contours of the mountain and canyon disappear, engulfed by darkness. Without competing light from nearby cities, stars filled every corner of the sky and it  sparkled like we&amp;#39;ve never seen it sparkle before. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the morning, we turned the Mesquite Sand Dunes into a playground. We jumped over smooth ridges and slid down slopes only to run back up - and bade farewell to Death Valley. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/death_valley/sand_dunes.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; height=&quot;340px&quot; width=&quot;520px&quot;&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Joshua Tree&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From Death Valley, we drove south to Joshua Tree National Park, home to curious trees, impressive boulders, and one memorable campground. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Arriving with an hour of daylight left, we were relieved that we didn&amp;#39;t have to venture far to enjoy the park. Even along the park&amp;#39;s main road, Joshua Trees were everywhere. They hugged the edge of the ashpalt and sprouted every few feet - if they were taller, we&amp;#39;d be driving through a forest - and their short, thick branches growing out like curved fingers reminded me of neurons, albeit in plant form. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/joshua_tree/joshua_trees.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; height=&quot;280px&quot; width=&quot;520px&quot;&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The trees share the park with massive rock formations, some of which are named after the shapes they resemble. Instead of settling for Skull Rock, which was crawling with tourists, we scrambled up until we reached a childhood friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/joshua_tree/bulbasaur_boulder.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; height=&quot;400px&quot; width=&quot;380px&quot;&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Bulbasaur Boulder&lt;/figcation&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a trip to Keys Point to watch the sun set over the Salton Sea, the snowcapped peak of Mt. San Jacinto, and the San Andras Fault, it was dark when we reached our campgrounds. But we could still make out the outline of large boulders - our campground was nestled within the same rock formations that we had just explored. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We set up our tent, making sure to carry extra blankets to combat the cold. With the help of a few newspapers from Albertson&amp;#39;s, we iterated on our tepee of firewood until our campfire roared - a first for both of us. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the morning, those large boulders became this: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/joshua_tree/camping.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; height=&quot;310px&quot; width=&quot;480px&quot;&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Our cozy corner&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naturally, we climbed to the top to ring in the last sunrise of 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/joshua_tree/view.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; height=&quot;320px&quot; width=&quot;480px&quot;&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We got a last look at the park by climbing to the top of Ryan Mountain. At 5,457 feet, those curious trees look more like shrubs and the impressive boulders more like pebbles, but Joshua Tree looks even more grand. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/joshua_tree/ryan_mountain.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; height=&quot;320px&quot; width=&quot;480px&quot;&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We left Joshua Tree and headed for San Diego. Immediately, we were reacquianted with the splendors of civilization: an hour long line to check into our hotel room, every minute of which made the previous 3 days a bit more precious. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;My wall has a new addition, a map of U.S. National Parks. Using tacks, Christine and I have turned the map into a playful game. My color is red, Christine’s is yellow. Green is for parks that we both have visited. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/california-np/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/california-np/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Everything in Belize Tastes Like Chicken</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Names are a cinch in Belize, just like the currency (1 US dollar = 2 Belize) or the language (English). The Old River that runs through Belize City is brackish, but the New River, to the northwest in Orange Walk, is freshwater. Hattieville is the settlement created in 1961 in the aftermath of Hurricane Hattie. The world’s largest cemetery bisected by highway is found on Cemetery Road. This easy-going attitude permeated the five days that Christine and I spent there in December 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We landed in Belize City in the early afternoon. The climate was inviting: warm, but not suffocating. Immediately, we saw the country’s mangrove ecosystem: dense green groves of tropical trees about fifteen feet high everywhere, especially along the river. Belize City itself is cobbled together. Run down homes and buildings are everywhere, half built, abandoned, wood rotting. The roads are dirt, or full of potholes. Thankfully, we expected this (having done our research), and took to the sea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Day 1: Ambergris Caye&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our first stop was San Pedro, the largest city on Ambergris Caye, Belize’s largest island. The waters of the Caribbean are gentle - playful even, compared to the Pacific. A 1.5 hr ferry ride carried us past mangroves and through splashes of tropical rain. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;San Pedro runs almost entirely north and south. It’s an approachable town - no more than a few streets wide - but busy. While walking to our hotel mid-afternoon, We passed a steady wave of golf carts and children in white uniforms walking home from school. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tired from our red eye flight, we headed to the west side of the island to eat dinner (cocktails, a delicious lobster burrito and grilled carne asada with rice). A few streets away, kids played basketball next to the ocean under the setting sun. We walked back with the rhythms of the town, and just like that, we were part of another carefree day in the Caribbean. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/belize/ambergis_caye.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; height=&quot;450px&quot; width=&quot;600px&quot;&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Day 2: Hol Chan Marine Reserve/Caye Caulker&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We woke early to watch the sunrise from the beach (the beauty of these islands - the sun rises and sets over beaches separated by blocks, not miles). Unfortunately, clouds blocked the sun and we didn’t see much. But all was well, because we were headed to Caye Caulker for a day of snorkeling, reggae music, and rum punch. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Caye Caulker is much smaller than Ambergris Caye. It’s also quieter, as the “Go Slow” motto beckons. Smiling owners run the stands along the beach, selling Belizan breakfast and fresh fruit smoothies, exuding the best type of island vibe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was my first time snorkeling in some time, and I had a little trouble getting my bearings. Luckily, I got them in time to experience the wonders of Hol Chan Marine Reserve. It’s amazing - viewed from the boat, the treasures of the ocean are expertly hidden, but an exotic and varied world exists only a few feet below. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hol Chan Marine Reserve is part of the world’s second largest barrier reef. Colorful corals cover the sea floor. They are crowded by schools of feeding fish, swaying in unison to the currents like the ripples of a wave. Larger fish floated by, lacking both urgency and a sense of direction. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/belize/hol_chan.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; height=&quot;400px&quot; width=&quot;600px&quot;&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At one point, the ocean floor dropped suddenly. The waters turned dramatic: darker, colder, more vast. Along the bottom of the floor, a manta ray drifted blithely forward. On our way back to the boat, we ran into a green eel moving about in its alien way. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We closed out the day drinking Belikins at the split, enjoying the sunset with vacationers from around the world, feeling festive and the perfect amount of tired, eagerly awaiting the next day. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/belize/the_split_belikin.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; height=&quot;450px&quot; width=&quot;600px&quot;&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Day 3: Lamanai&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Belize, being an English speaking country that accepts US dollars, may have felt like an extension of home, but thousands of years ago, it was part of the Mayan Empire. On our second full day, we explored Lamanai (Mayan for submerged crocodile), a major civilization center thousands of years ago. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our trip had two legs: by car and by boat along the New River. Ever since touring Tibet in 2010, I’ve loved sitting in cars in foreign lands, doing nothing but pondering the surrounding landscape. What I found striking about the Belize countryside is just how green it is. The color dominates the plant life - I was hard pressed to find even an orange or white flower. All the trees are all around the same height as well, and the homogeneity is defining. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to heavy rain the week before, the New River overflowed its banks by about 4 feet. Considering that many streams in California today can barely afford a trickle, the river felt particularly full and vibrant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/belize/new_river.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; height=&quot;450px&quot; width=&quot;600px&quot;&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We got a personal peek at wildlife on the river. Within minutes of boarding, a spider monkey with freakishly long limbs ventured close, seeking out the food he was accustomed to getting from tour boats like ours. When the river widened into a lagoon an hour later, we arrived. Immediately, we heard the frightening howl of howler monkeys, who wield their howl to protect their territory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First inhabited around 16th Century B.C., Lamanai contains a series of temple ruins in the middle of the jungle. Today, many of the temples mounds have been reclaimed by nature, and lie covered by a rumble of dirt. The few unearthed temples are beautiful. Their sizes are imposing, their symmetry gives them aesthetic appeal, and their uniqueness conjuring images up the ancient world that they belonged to. We climbed atop the steps of the highest temple (aptly named High Temple) to enjoy the view. With the New River at our backs, surrounded by miles of the verdant jungle canopy, I pictured nighttime ritual sacrifices, illuminated by flames from the temples, emanating life like the gods they reverently honored.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/belize/high_temple.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; height=&quot;450px&quot; width=&quot;600px&quot;&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we headed back to Belize City in the mid-afternoon, we were more than ready to escape the unrelenting swarm of mosquitoes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Day 4: Zip-lining, ATVs&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It rained heavily all day, which foiled our original plan to go cave tubing. Instead, we went back to the jungle for zip-lining and ATV riding. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The heavy rain brought out our adventurous spirit. We were soaked, but zipping. At times, the rain came down so hard it was tough to open our eyes. But when we could, we saw the familiar vastness of the jungle, this time spread across the slopes of hills and above streams swollen with muddy waters. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I have never ridden an ATV before, much less through the mud swamped jungle, it was an unforgettable experience. Our vehicles handled the terrain effortlessly, powering over rocks and protruding branches and makeshift ponds. It was fun coaxing the ATV by angling our bodies and surveying the path to pick the routes with the best mix of adventure and safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/belize/atv.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; height=&quot;450px&quot; width=&quot;600px&quot;&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the ride, we waded across a slippery stream that reached our waist. The ground was slippery and our guide was the first to fall in. Of course, I was next. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a fitting end to our stay in Belize, a country where nature dictates the splendors and the dangers, the experiences and the casualties (one of my favorite shirts, covered in mud, and our skin, covered in mosquito bites).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Names are a cinch in Belize, just like the currency (1 US dollar = 2 Belize) or the language (English). The Old River that runs through Belize City is brackish, but the New River, to the northwest in Orange Walk, is freshwater. Hattieville is the settlement created in 1961 in the aftermath of Hurricane Hattie. The world’s largest cemetery bisected by highway is found on Cemetery Road. This easy-going attitude permeated the five days that Christine and I spent there in December 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/everything-in-belize-tastes-like-chicken/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/everything-in-belize-tastes-like-chicken/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Back to Nature</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After the bombardment of light, sound, color, and skin at scorching EDC Las Vegas, we enjoyed this weekend getaway like one savors a light, seductive touch to the forearm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We started early Saturday, exploring Monterey Bay on kayak, paddling level with birds majestically grazing the ocean surface. First, we saw sea lions, masters of slumber, who had fully claimed the rocks protruding from the shore. We then stopped to observe sea otters. Upon seeing them floating, Christine ignored me completely; I don’t blame her for favoring the mother otter, who spends up to eight months with her child held against her belly, a selfless shield from perils lurking below, over me. Turning into an inlet, our guide directed us to crabs teeming like a horrifying mass of spiders and scooped up a plump sea slug that briefly dyed Christine’s hand purple. After parking our kayaks on the beach, we peeled off our wetsuits, revealing impressive sunburns. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, after a few hours at the Monterey Bay Aquarium, we drove to Point Lobos State Park, where the ocean enlivens the rocks into a jagged mixture of layer and pattern. Arm in arm, Christine and I ambled along the rugged California Coast, letting last week&amp;#39;s anthems fade into darkness. At night, we gazed at an organic electric sky on Del Monte Beach - a saturation of orange and pink and yellow, the most brilliant sunset I have seen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/sunset.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; height=&quot;340px&quot; width=&quot;520px&quot;&gt;&gt; 
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At noon on Sunday, we hit the surf with our (limited) abilities. For the next two hours, I was liberated, fully engaged, entranced by the waves and the smooth, glass-like water. For the rest of my life, I’ll feel myself pushing up with my arms. I&amp;#39;ll prepare for the ensuing tumble. I’ll intimate my underdeveloped sense of balance. I’ll watch Christine rise to her feet, one cautious knee at a time - my girlfriend, consistently rising to the challenge. I’ll see my two feet and realize that I’m upright on my only successful ride to the shore, weightless and giddy from the curve of the wave. I won’t be able to describe how it happened, only that I need to experience it again, and again, and again. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Midway through the drive back home, I fell asleep. When I woke up and reflected on our new experiences, I found a ribbon - the only prize I need for being a participant of the world. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;After the bombardment of light, sound, color, and skin at scorching EDC Las Vegas, we enjoyed this weekend getaway like one savors a light, seductive touch to the forearm.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/back-to-nature/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/back-to-nature/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Pacific Northwest, Day 3</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Crater Lake is a gift, a display of nature’s genius when the conditions are just right. The clear, blue water dominates the senses, extending almost as far as the eyes can see. On a good day like today, the clouds float in the water. The lake exudes tranquility - some silences are ring forever - and even the wildlife know they are lucky to be there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that being said, at this time of the year, there’s not a whole lot to do in Crater Lake.
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater_lake_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;figcaption&gt;Definitely worth more than a thousand of my words&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I want to record something more important about today. I’ve been with Christine since Thursday afternoon, by far the longest time I have ever spent with someone. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, the indefensible. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christine doesn’t like cilantro. Her membership amongst the fun deprived, friendless citizens of the world is confirmed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To the defensible. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She appreciates every moment, capturing its beauty through a photo trail of her life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She likes to go ‘Wheeeee’ when passing a sluggish driver, because the world is her playground. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She will put up with a lot in the name of good adventure, including an easily distracted navigator and an inexperienced rafter. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She is a skilled reader, quick to discern what’s important and what’s not. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She knows what she doesn’t know, but doesn’t let it get in the way of what she wants to know. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I learned a lot this trip to the Pacific Northwest, and saw unforgettable sights. But when it&amp;#39;s all said and done, I&amp;#39;ll remember how Christine&amp;#39;s smile made me beam and that her laugh is a required nutrient for my soul. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/rafting.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; height=&quot;520px&quot; width=&quot;380px&quot;&gt;&gt; 
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Crater Lake is a gift, a display of nature’s genius when the conditions are just right. The clear, blue water dominates the senses, extending almost as far as the eyes can see. On a good day like today, the clouds float in the water. The lake exudes tranquility - some silences are ring forever - and even the wildlife know they are lucky to be there.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/pacific-northwest-day-3/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/pacific-northwest-day-3/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Pacific Northwest, Day 2</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today was about learning. Christine and I talked about concepts we never really grasped, navigated the pulse of Southern Oregon, and found new ways to take on the world as a team of two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I woke up early, walked around Ashland, and started hoarding information about Crater Lake. For the next hour, armed with curiosity, Christine and I launched into hypothetical scenarios, emptying America’s deepest lake on a whim and instantly refilling it with 250 years worth of evaporation, rainfall, and snowmelt. At brunch, an orange peel became a convex lens, but metamorphic powers weren’t enough to fully understand cameras. The egg biscuit sandwich, on the other hand, was easy to describe. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The residents of Shady Cove, Oregon, our next stop are down to earth and honest - it’s tough not to be when living along the Rogue River. It compels a new father to wade knee deep in the water, daughter strapped on his back. Fisherman, drawn by the promise of salmon, go out in droves - families, grills, 50 stars and 13 stripes in tow in their F150s. When we ask about the next fish, it’s the river that responds with realism, humor and warmth. For software engineers from San Francisco, the river is a wave that breaks onto Christine during a failed attempt to ta a current. Eventually, we learned when to carve our oars deep into the water and when to gently graze the surface, and we were free to connect with the homeowners along the river bank. We floated by to their smiles and waves, happy to share together the unrelenting ebb and flow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/rogue_river.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; height=&quot;420px&quot; width=&quot;600px&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;figcaption&gt;Our view for 3 hours&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christine and I chased our large pizza down with cold beer that night. Next time, we&amp;#39;ll take that Hawaiian Pizza and refreshing blonde ale back to the river. We&amp;#39;ll invite all the fisherman to join us (mainly to play with their dogs), and we’ll take a big ol&amp;#39; breath of that good ol&amp;#39; American air.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Today was about learning. Christine and I talked about concepts we never really grasped, navigated the pulse of Southern Oregon, and found new ways to take on the world as a team of two.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/pacific-northwest-day-2/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/pacific-northwest-day-2/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Pacific Northwest, Day 1</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We woke up and dutifully typed something about working from home. Before the words reached our colleges, we were on the the road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Molded by volcanic eruptions, Lassen Volcanic National Park is home to fascinating natural phenomena, the first of which was set against an backdrop of pine trees, boulders, and streams. Stepping out of the car, we found ourselves in the middle of an ancient volcano. A few miles below, raging magna activated steam, fumaroles and boiling mudpots, and the stench of rotten eggs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We continued on, stopping at a lake that appeared amongst the branches. I took a moment to enjoy the sounds of nature. When I opened my eyes, I saw Christine making her way across a tree trunk that had fallen into the water, eyes straight ahead, her steady determination the only soul in sight. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/summit_lake.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; height=&quot;420px&quot; width=&quot;600px&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;figcaption&gt;Next time we&#39;ll go for a swim&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The touch of fate blessed us for the rest of the day. After a hike around a lily pond, it started to rain. We plunged into a lava tube, a third of a mile long and pitch black. In my heart I like to believe that the flow of lava naturally creates a tunnel to one day help astonished travelers stay dry. Later, driving next to Mt. Shasta, we took a wrong turn. I heard a gasp - a few feet in front of us, three black bears were crossing the road. We watched as a cub swiftly climbed a tree, disappearing into the forest, leaving us in excited awe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We entered Oregon under a vibrant pink and orange sky, the vastness of the land etched vividly into our minds. Here’s to scattering the imagery of today into our dreams, and recalling the memories of today often throughout our lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;We woke up and dutifully typed something about working from home. Before the words reached our colleges, we were on the the road.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/pacific-northwest-day-1/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/pacific-northwest-day-1/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Alcatraz</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Some periods in life are covered by clouds, periods when what you don’t have makes it hard to appreciate all that you are blessed with. It’s during these times that simple interactions standout the most. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My senior year of college was such a time. My mind was weighed down by clouds I could not escape. I was at the end of four years in Berkeley, equally weary of partying and studying. Most of all, I was lonely and a virgin, watching from the sidelines as my friends lived  carefree lives with their girlfriends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4uD73765nt4&quot;&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&amp;quot;Waiting for the clouds to part, waiting to be out of the dark &lt;/br&gt;
If our future’s bright, then the present is overcast &lt;/br&gt;
And we want it to be over fast, lets shine&amp;quot;&lt;/br&gt;
Waiting for the Clouds - Nujabes &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christine joined the fraternity I was in during our sophomore year. We became part of the same friend group, but didn’t get to know each other until two years later. After a night in Las Vegas, we unexpectedly found ourselves bonding over growing up Asian in the suburbs, eventually getting escorted off restricted ground by Caesar Palace security guards. I remember how her presence made me feel at ease, momentarily parting a few clouds from my sky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We moved three blocks from one another after graduating college. Embracing life in San Francisco, we spent the weekends clubbing and bar hopping, and inventing excuses to eat carne asada fries. The comfort I felt with her grew. I noticed how incredibly kind she was, saw how much she loved and cared for her friends. I looked forward to her company because it was so easy being around her. Plus, she was always ready for an adventure. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=129kuDCQtHs&quot;&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
“You can’t start a fire, you can’t start a fire without a spark&lt;/br&gt;
This gun’s for hire, even if we’re just dancing in the dark&amp;quot; &lt;/br&gt;
Dancing in the Dark - Bruce Springsteen &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christine and I started dating in early March 2015. Walks through the city after foosball and Chinese food replaced Bootie and Origin.  Above &amp;amp; Beyond at the Bill Graham Theater was one of my best nights of my life. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Bll6rQIQaVc&quot;&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
“No I never had a night like this, &lt;/br&gt;
 No I never had a night like this  &lt;/br&gt;
I ain’t never shine bright like this  &lt;/br&gt;
It’s more than beautiful, more than beautiful&amp;quot; &lt;/br&gt;
Top of the World - OCD: Moosh &amp;amp; Twist  &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s been almost a year since we moved to San Francisco. Lights from the Bay Bridge no longer enliven a long commute back to limited privacy. With the novelty of living in the city fading, we needed a change in perspective. Last Sunday, Christine and I took the ferry to Alcatraz Island. As night fell, we followed in the footsteps of America’s most notorious prisoners to the top of a hill. Below us, birds crooned at one another, oblivious to the world around them. As I put my arm around Christine, the magnificent San Francisco skyline formed in front us. I couldn’t have imagined a better view: there wasn&amp;#39;t a single cloud in the sky. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VQs9hco8HVw&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
“Take me to a place &lt;/br&gt;
Where we both don’t have to face &lt;/br&gt;
The things we faked &lt;/br&gt;
There’ll be nothing on my mind&amp;quot; &lt;/br&gt;
Nothing On My Mind - Astronomyy &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Some periods in life are covered by clouds, periods when what you don’t have makes it hard to appreciate all that you are blessed with. It’s during these times that simple interactions standout the most. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/alcatraz/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/alcatraz/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>
