<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CLoh and JZhang Take On The World</title>
    <description>Long Form Jekyll theme built with SASS / COMPASS / SUSY</description>
    <link>http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2015 02:11:46 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 May 2015 02:11:46 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Alcatraz</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Some periods in life are covered by clouds, periods when what you don’t have makes it hard to appreciate all that you are blessed with. It’s during these times that simple interactions standout the most. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My senior year of college was such a time. My mind was weighed down by clouds I could not escape. I was at the end of four years in Berkeley, equally weary of partying and studying. Most of all, I was lonely and a virgin, watching from the sidelines as my friends lived  carefree lives with their girlfriends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4uD73765nt4&quot;&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&amp;quot;Waiting for the clouds to part, waiting to be out of the dark &lt;/br&gt;
If our future’s bright, then the present is overcast &lt;/br&gt;
And we want it to be over fast, lets shine&amp;quot;&lt;/br&gt;
Waiting for the Clouds - Nujabes &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christine joined the fraternity I was in during our sophomore year. We became part of the same friend group, but didn’t get to know each other until two years later. After a night in Las Vegas, we unexpectedly found ourselves bonding over growing up Asian in the suburbs, eventually getting escorted off restricted ground by Caesar Palace security guards. I remember how her presence made me feel at ease, momentarily parting a few clouds from my sky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We moved three blocks from one another after graduating college. Embracing life in San Francisco, we spent the weekends clubbing and bar hopping, and inventing excuses to eat carne asada fries. The comfort I felt with her grew. I noticed how incredibly kind she was, saw how much she loved and cared for her friends. I looked forward to her company because it was so easy being around her. Plus, she was always ready for an adventure. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=129kuDCQtHs&quot;&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
“You can’t start a fire, you can’t start a fire without a spark&lt;/br&gt;
This gun’s for hire, even if we’re just dancing in the dark&amp;quot; &lt;/br&gt;
Dancing in the Dark - Bruce Springsteen &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christine and I started dating in early March 2015. Walks through the city after foosball and Chinese food replaced Bootie and Origin.  Above &amp;amp; Beyond at the Bill Graham Theater was one of my best nights of my life. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Bll6rQIQaVc&quot;&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
“No I never had a night like this, &lt;/br&gt;
 No I never had a night like this  &lt;/br&gt;
I ain’t never shine bright like this  &lt;/br&gt;
It’s more than beautiful, more than beautiful&amp;quot; &lt;/br&gt;
Top of the World - OCD: Moosh &amp;amp; Twist  &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s been almost a year since we moved to San Francisco. Lights from the Bay Bridge no longer enliven a long commute back to limited privacy. With the novelty of living in the city fading, we needed a change in perspective. Last Sunday, Christine and I took the ferry to Alcatraz Island. As night fell, we followed in the footsteps of America’s most notorious prisoners to the top of a hill. Below us, birds crooned at one another, oblivious to the world around them. As I put my arm around Christine, the magnificent San Francisco skyline formed in front us. I couldn’t have imagined a better view: there wasn&amp;#39;t a single cloud in the sky. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VQs9hco8HVw&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
“Take me to a place &lt;/br&gt;
Where we both don’t have to face &lt;/br&gt;
The things we faked &lt;/br&gt;
There’ll be nothing on my mind&amp;quot; &lt;/br&gt;
Nothing On My Mind - Astronomyy &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Some periods in life are covered by clouds, periods when what you don’t have makes it hard to appreciate all that you are blessed with. It’s during these times that simple interactions standout the most. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/alcatraz/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/alcatraz/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>
