<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christine and Jimmy Take On The World</title>
    <description>Long Form Jekyll theme built with SASS / COMPASS / SUSY</description>
    <link>http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 23:08:40 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 23:08:40 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Angel Island</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m reading Cool Gray City of Love, 49 vignettes about places in San Francisco. Each chapter is a separate story - only Kamira’s dedication to his city ties them together - histories of people and the land they walked on woven together with personal experiences. The writing is reverent, a poetic tribute, and I heard its echoes throughout our trip to Angel Island on Sunday. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bike ride from Christine’s apartment to the Angel Island Ferry is as smooth as any in the city - a straight shot down Valencia, right on Market until the shimmering bay, capped by a cruise down Embarcadero. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m reading Cool Gray City of Love, 49 vignettes about places in San Francisco. Each chapter is a separate story - only Kamira’s dedication to his city ties them together - histories of people and the land they walked on woven together with personal experiences. The writing is reverent, a poetic tribute, and I heard its echoes throughout our trip to Angel Island on Sunday. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/angel-island/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/angel-island/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>A Spattering of Memories</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I remember you once wrote a quick list about me, to get the writing juices flowing again. Well, here I am writing about you, because I haven’t written in a while either, and I want to relive some of our memories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I enjoyed our friendship before we started dating. I felt there always existed a certain understanding between us. One time there were a few of us in a car, probably me, Jacquie, and Rich, and you asked me what we were up to. I forgot what I said but we picked you up at Avalon. I forgot where we went but I remember you wore the most genuine “YAY” face as you got into the car. Knowing us, we probably all snorted yay in the bathroom. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometime after Bootie, I went on a second Coffee Meets Bagel date with a girl named Pia. We were supposed to do yoga in the morning but I woke up hungover, and I think she did too, so we got coffee instead. Near the end of the date I told her I was seeing another girl. She asked me who the lucky girl was; I said her name was Christine. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soon after we started dating, we went six weeks without a weekend together. You were in Taiwan and at Coachella and I was in Montreal and Chicago. Between us, we posted so many Instagrams even Jacquie noticed how long it had been. On our first Friday together, we proceeded to do mushrooms. I needed to pee and Whitney was taking a shower, so I ran downstairs without my shoes. I started to trip hard, and I dragged you out into the rain with me. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those six weekends apart were rough, but luckily, we hung out during the week because we lived so close. One particular Tuesday was a glorious sequence of events: your roommates left so we immediately started having sex. You came and we got dressed and headed straight to the best pizza place in North Beach I could find on Yelp. With happy bodies and a full stomach, we walked up to Coit Tower, overlooking the gorgeous Bay at night, back when the Bay Bridge was still lit with life. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The road trip to Oregon was the highlight of my year. We rafted down the Rogue River, it almost took your keys. I will never forget seeing Crater Lake, the most singularly beautiful sight I&amp;#39;ve seen, for the first time. We paid our homage by eating a whole bag of Chex Mix in front of it, not saying much, keeping our eyes on that pristine blue. On the way back, the snow-capped Mt. Shasta peak blended in perfect harmony with the clouds. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We went to EDC and folk danced to Avicii. The next weekend we were in Monterey Bay, eating Chex Mix again along each mile of the 19-mile drive. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More recently, we biked to Outside Lands and brought the “folk” dance back for Mumford and Sons. We sat on a baseball field in San Carlos and counted shooting stars. I watched as you packed for New York City. You were listing the items you needed: socks, contacts, jackets, all that good stuff. You came up to me, tried to fold me up and tried to take me with you. It was so cute. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s to the next batch of memories, grand and mundane, triumphant and silly, that we will create together. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;I remember you once wrote a quick list about me, to get the writing juices flowing again. Well, here I am writing about you, because I haven’t written in a while either, and I want to relive some of our memories.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/a-spattering-of-memories/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/a-spattering-of-memories/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Back to Nature</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After the bombardment of light, sound, color, and skin at scorching EDC Las Vegas, we enjoyed this weekend getaway like one savors a light, seductive touch to the forearm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We started early Saturday, exploring Monterey Bay on kayak, paddling level with birds majestically grazing the ocean surface. First, we saw sea lions, masters of slumber, who had fully claimed the rocks protruding from the shore. We then stopped to observe sea otters. Upon seeing them floating, Christine ignored me completely; I don’t blame her for favoring the mother otter, who spends up to eight months with her child held against her belly, a selfless shield from perils lurking below, over me. Turning into an inlet, our guide directed us to crabs teeming like a horrifying mass of spiders and scooped up a plump sea slug that briefly dyed Christine’s hand purple. After parking our kayaks on the beach, we peeled off our wetsuits, revealing impressive sunburns. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, after a few hours at the Monterey Bay Aquarium, we drove to Point Lobos State Park, where the ocean enlivens the rocks into a jagged mixture of layer and pattern. Arm in arm, Christine and I ambled along the rugged California Coast, letting last week&amp;#39;s anthems fade into darkness. At night, we gazed at an organic electric sky on Del Monte Beach - a saturation of orange and pink and yellow, the most brilliant sunset I have seen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/sunset.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt; 
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At noon on Sunday, we hit the surf with our (limited) abilities. For the next two hours, I was liberated, fully engaged, entranced by the waves, the smooth, glass-like water. For the rest of my life, I’ll feel myself pushing up with my arms. I&amp;#39;ll prepare for the ensuing tumble. I’ll intimate my underdeveloped sense of balance. I’ll watch Christine rise to her feet, one cautious knee at a time - my girlfriend, consistently rising to the challenge. I’ll see my two feet and realize that I’m upright on my only successful ride to the shore, weightless and giddy from the curve of the wave. I won’t be able to describe how it happened, only that I need to experience it again, and again, and again. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Midway through the drive back home, I fell asleep. When I woke up and reflected on our new experiences, I found a ribbon - the only prize I need for being a participant of the world. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;After the bombardment of light, sound, color, and skin at scorching EDC Las Vegas, we enjoyed this weekend getaway like one savors a light, seductive touch to the forearm.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/back-to-nature/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/back-to-nature/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Pacific Northwest, Day 3</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Crater Lake is a gift, a display of nature’s genius when the conditions are just right. The clear, blue water dominates the senses, extending almost as far as the eyes can see. On a good day like today, the clouds float in the water. The lake exudes tranquility - some silences are ring forever - and even the wildlife know they are lucky to be there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that being said, at this time of the year, there’s not a whole lot to do in Crater Lake.
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater_lake_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;figcaption&gt;Definitely worth more than a thousand of my words&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I want to record something more important about today. I’ve been with Christine since Thursday afternoon, by far the longest time I have ever spent with someone. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, the indefensible. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christine doesn’t like cilantro. Her membership amongst the fun deprived, friendless citizens of the world is confirmed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To the defensible. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She appreciates every moment, capturing its beauty through a photo trail of her life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She likes to go ‘Wheeeee’ when passing a sluggish driver, because the world is her playground. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She will put up with a lot in the name of good adventure, including an easily distracted navigator and an inexperienced rafter. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She is a skilled reader, quick to discern what’s important and what’s not. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She knows what she doesn’t know, but doesn’t let it get in the way of what she wants to know. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I learned a lot this trip to the Pacific Northwest, and saw unforgettable sights. But when it&amp;#39;s all said and done, I&amp;#39;ll remember how Christine&amp;#39;s smile made me beam and that her laugh is a required nutrient for my soul. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/rafting.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt; 
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Crater Lake is a gift, a display of nature’s genius when the conditions are just right. The clear, blue water dominates the senses, extending almost as far as the eyes can see. On a good day like today, the clouds float in the water. The lake exudes tranquility - some silences are ring forever - and even the wildlife know they are lucky to be there.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/pacific-northwest-day-3/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/pacific-northwest-day-3/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Pacific Northwest, Day 2</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today was about learning. Christine and I talked about concepts we never really grasped, navigated the pulse of Southern Oregon, and found new ways to take on the world as a team of two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I woke up early, walked around Ashland, and started hoarding information about Crater Lake. For the next hour, armed with curiosity, Christine and I launched into hypothetical scenarios, emptying America’s deepest lake on a whim and instantly refilling it with 250 years worth of evaporation, rainfall, and snowmelt. At brunch, an orange peel became a convex lens, but metamorphic powers weren’t enough to fully understand cameras. The egg biscuit sandwich, on the other hand, was easy to describe. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The residents of our next stop - Shady Cove, Oregeon - are down to earth and honest. It’s impossible not to be when living along the Rogue River. Nothing else can compel a new father to wade knee deep in the water, daughter strapped on his back. Fisherman, drawn by the promise of salmon, go out in droves - families, grills, 50 stars and 13 stripes in tow in their F150s. When we ask about the next fish, it’s the river that responds with realism, humor and warmth. For software engineers from San Francisco, the river is a wave that breaks onto Christine in a failed attempt to raft head on into a current. Eventually, we learned when to carve our oars deep into the water and when to gently graze the surface, and we were free to connect with the homeowners along the river bank. We floated by to their smiles and waves, happy to share together the unrelenting ebb and flow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/rogue_river.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;figcaption&gt;Our view for 3 hours&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christine and I chased our large pizza down with cold beer that night. Next time, we&amp;#39;ll take that Hawaiian Pizza and refreshing blonde ale back to the river. We&amp;#39;ll invite all the fisherman to join us (mainly to play with their dogs), and we’ll take a big ol&amp;#39; breath of that good ol&amp;#39; American air.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Today was about learning. Christine and I talked about concepts we never really grasped, navigated the pulse of Southern Oregon, and found new ways to take on the world as a team of two.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/pacific-northwest-day-2/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/pacific-northwest-day-2/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Pacific Northwest, Day 1</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We woke up and dutifully typed something about working from home. Before the words reached our colleges, we were on the the road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Molded by volcanic eruptions, Lassen Volcanic National Park is home to fascinating natural phenomena, the first of which was set against an backdrop of pine trees, boulders, and streams. Stepping out of the car, we found ourselves in the middle of an ancient volcano. A few miles below, raging magna activated steam, fumaroles and boiling mudpots, and the stench of rotten eggs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We continued on, stopping at a lake that appeared amongst the branches. I took a moment to enjoy the sounds of nature. When I opened my eyes, I saw Christine making her way across a tree trunk that had fallen into the water, eyes straight ahead, her steady determination the only soul in sight. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/summit_lake.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;figcaption&gt;Next time we&#39;ll go for a swim&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The touch of fate blessed us for the rest of the day. After a hike around a lily pond, it started to rain. We plunged into a lava tube, a third of a mile long and pitch black. In my heart I like to believe that the flow of lava naturally creates a tunnel to one day help astonished travelers stay dry. Later, driving next to Mt. Shasta, we took a wrong turn. I heard a gasp - a few feet in front of us, three black bears were crossing the road. We watched as a cub swiftly climbed a tree, disappearing into the forest, leaving us in excited awe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We entered Oregon under a vibrant pink and orange sky, the vastness of the land etched vividly into our minds. Here’s to scattering the imagery of today into our dreams, and recalling the memories of today often throughout our lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;We woke up and dutifully typed something about working from home. Before the words reached our colleges, we were on the the road.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/pacific-northwest-day-1/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/pacific-northwest-day-1/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Alcatraz</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Some periods in life are covered by clouds, periods when what you don’t have makes it hard to appreciate all that you are blessed with. It’s during these times that simple interactions standout the most. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My senior year of college was such a time. My mind was weighed down by clouds I could not escape. I was at the end of four years in Berkeley, equally weary of partying and studying. Most of all, I was lonely and a virgin, watching from the sidelines as my friends lived  carefree lives with their girlfriends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4uD73765nt4&quot;&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&amp;quot;Waiting for the clouds to part, waiting to be out of the dark &lt;/br&gt;
If our future’s bright, then the present is overcast &lt;/br&gt;
And we want it to be over fast, lets shine&amp;quot;&lt;/br&gt;
Waiting for the Clouds - Nujabes &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christine joined the fraternity I was in during our sophomore year. We became part of the same friend group, but didn’t get to know each other until two years later. After a night in Las Vegas, we unexpectedly found ourselves bonding over growing up Asian in the suburbs, eventually getting escorted off restricted ground by Caesar Palace security guards. I remember how her presence made me feel at ease, momentarily parting a few clouds from my sky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We moved three blocks from one another after graduating college. Embracing life in San Francisco, we spent the weekends clubbing and bar hopping, and inventing excuses to eat carne asada fries. The comfort I felt with her grew. I noticed how incredibly kind she was, saw how much she loved and cared for her friends. I looked forward to her company because it was so easy being around her. Plus, she was always ready for an adventure. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=129kuDCQtHs&quot;&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
“You can’t start a fire, you can’t start a fire without a spark&lt;/br&gt;
This gun’s for hire, even if we’re just dancing in the dark&amp;quot; &lt;/br&gt;
Dancing in the Dark - Bruce Springsteen &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christine and I started dating in early March 2015. Walks through the city after foosball and Chinese food replaced Bootie and Origin.  Above &amp;amp; Beyond at the Bill Graham Theater was one of my best nights of my life. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Bll6rQIQaVc&quot;&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
“No I never had a night like this, &lt;/br&gt;
 No I never had a night like this  &lt;/br&gt;
I ain’t never shine bright like this  &lt;/br&gt;
It’s more than beautiful, more than beautiful&amp;quot; &lt;/br&gt;
Top of the World - OCD: Moosh &amp;amp; Twist  &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s been almost a year since we moved to San Francisco. Lights from the Bay Bridge no longer enliven a long commute back to limited privacy. With the novelty of living in the city fading, we needed a change in perspective. Last Sunday, Christine and I took the ferry to Alcatraz Island. As night fell, we followed in the footsteps of America’s most notorious prisoners to the top of a hill. Below us, birds crooned at one another, oblivious to the world around them. As I put my arm around Christine, the magnificent San Francisco skyline formed in front us. I couldn’t have imagined a better view: there wasn&amp;#39;t a single cloud in the sky. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VQs9hco8HVw&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
“Take me to a place &lt;/br&gt;
Where we both don’t have to face &lt;/br&gt;
The things we faked &lt;/br&gt;
There’ll be nothing on my mind&amp;quot; &lt;/br&gt;
Nothing On My Mind - Astronomyy &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Some periods in life are covered by clouds, periods when what you don’t have makes it hard to appreciate all that you are blessed with. It’s during these times that simple interactions standout the most. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/alcatraz/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://brianmaierjr.github.com/long-haul/blog/alcatraz/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>
